So we've loaded in our transaction data and split it into training and test sets.
我们加载了交易数据并将数据拆分为训练集和测试集
Now, it's time to define the model that we want to train.
下面开始定义我们要训练的模型
In this exercise, we'll utilize siege makers linear learner,
在这道练习中 我们将使用 SageMaker 的 LinearLearner
which has two main applications.
LinearLearner 主要有两个用途
One is for regression tasks in which a linear line is fit to some data points.
一个是完成回归任务 即用一条线拟合数据点
In this case, you want a model that can produce a predicted output value given
你希望模型能根据某些数据点生成预测输出值
some data point such as predicting the price of a house given its square size.
例如根据平方尺寸预测房价
The second use is to do binary classification,
第二个用途是执行二元分类
in which the linear learner basically learns a line to separate two classes of data.
LinearLearner 会学习一条能区分两类数据的直线
It effectively outputs labels,
它会输出一个标签
either the class label one for data that falls above
数据点在这条线上方的类别标签为 1
the line or zero for points that fall on or below the line.
数据点在这条线上或下面的类别标签为 0
This is a simple two-dimensional case,
这是一个简单的二维示例
but you can think of this as a plane or multi-dimensional line for multiple features.
还可以将其看做平面或针对多个特征的多维直线
In our case, we'll want to use this as a binary classifier and use it to
对我们来说 我们会将 LinearLearner 当做二元分类器
predict our two transaction classes valid zero, or fraudulent one.
并用它预测两个交易类别 有效交易标签为 0 欺诈性交易标签为 1
As with any machine learning method,
与任何机器学习方法一样
we'll first train our linear learner on
我们首先将用现有训练数据训练 LinearLearner
some existing training data so it can learn a good separation line.
使其学习一条很好的分隔线
Then we'll apply it to some new test data to see how it generalizes and performs.
然后将模型应用到新的测试数据上 看看泛化效果
You can instantiate a linear learner in the same way that we've been doing other models,
你可以像任何其他模型一样实例化 LinearLearner
parsing in some constructor hyper-parameters,
传入一些构造函数超参数 角色
the role and output location in addition to specific model hyper-parameters.
输出位置以及特定于模型的超参数
For your next exercise,
对于下道练习
I've given you a link to the linear learner documentation,
我提供了 LinearLearner 参考文档的链接
that should give you enough information to create a linear learner estimator.
阅读该文档应该就足以创建一个 LinearLearner estimator 了
When you click on this link,
打开该文档后
you'll see that there are a lot of parameters you can parse in.
你会发现有很多参数可以传入
But I'd suggest only parsing in a few,
但我建议仅传入几个就行了
like the rule and training instance types,
例如角色 训练实例的类型
as well as specifying that we do indeed want a binary classifier.
并指定我们要使用二元分类器
You can leave most of the parameters as the default value.
大多数参数都可以保留默认值
If we complete this step,
完成这一步后
you're welcome to move on to converting our training data,
请继续转换训练数据
training an estimator, and even deploying it.
训练 estimator 甚至部署 estimator
In the next video, I'll go over one solution to creating a LinearLearner model.
在下个视频中 我将介绍我是如何创建 LinearLearner 模型的
Then later, we'll go over
之后 我们将学习
a few specific parameters and improve this model one step at a time.
几个特定的参数并一步步地改进此模型